milegend.com 2002-12-04

# Privacy Policy LFNetwork.com

LFNetwork.com is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors to our web site. By using this site, you are agreeing with the LFNetwork Privacy policy (see below). If however you do not agree with this policy, then do not provide any personal information to us. 

Collection of information  
Providing us with any personal information is not a requirement to access our main site, however certain information may be asked for in order for you to use certain services we provide, some of these situations include: 

\- Using the LucasForums.com (Bulletin Board System / message board) 

\- Participating in any contests or competitions we may run 

\- Sending us any requests for information, or emailing us and expecting a reply 

\- Providing other users on the BBS a means to contact you should they need to 

we also track certain information about visitors to get a better picture of who we are serving. This is so we can make the network more enjoyable for the target audience This information includes: 

\- Demographic Information 

\- Where a user has come from previous to visiting the site 

\- where a user goes to afterwards 

Any such information is gathered through the use of online forms and cookies (see below) and will be used only by LFNetwork and its affiliate sites for the purposes listed above 

Cookies  
Cookies are small pieces of electronic information, which a web site can store on a visitors hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies are very widely used on the Internet, and on many large company sites they are commonplace. 

At LFNetwork we use cookies only for the use of storing your Mixnmojo username and password on your computer, saving you logging in every time you visit the site. 

Links  
LFNetwork regularly creates links to the web sites of other parties we make every effort to link only to sites that carry the same standards of maintaining privacy of users. These pages may however link to other sites that do not meet our requirements. We cannot be held responsible for any material on sites other that on LFNetwork whether we link to them or are linked from them, or any links they may provide. 

Data Security and Protection  
Any Information we gather is stored online in a database on our server, backups may be made to offline locations. Integrity and security of data is a very important issue to us so we will abide by all 8 principles in the data protection act of 1984 

You always have the right to unsubscribe from any of our features, or ask us to delete any information we may have stored about you or any persons related to you. We also retain the right to change our Privacy policy at any time or delete any information we store. 

For further information on our privacy policy or any questions about information Mixnmojo has stored on you, or to correct or delete any information Mixnmojo may have about you or persons related to you please contact us. 

Advertising 

Third Party Advertising  
Some of the ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please click [here](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy). 

Third Party Cookies  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.
